Dunya Ramicova Costume Design Collection MSS.004
University of California, Merced Library
- Production Materials, Ephemera, and Process Notes, 66 Boxes
  - Box 115
    - Mathis der Maler - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for all Characters – Preliminary and Corrected; Artist Measurements; Research, Dressing Lists, Fabric Swatches, and Photographs from Costume Fittings (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Mathis der Maler - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for all Characters – Preliminary and Corrected; Artist Measurements; Research, Dressing Lists, Fabric Swatches, and Photographs from Costume Fittings (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Mathis der Maler - Pre-production Publicity (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Mathis der Maler - Playbill (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Mathis der Maler - Reviews (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Box 116
    - Don Juan - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Liviu Ciulei (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Don Juan - Visual Research (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Don Juan - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Don Juan - Costume Production Reference: Fabric Swatches (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Don Juan - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Don Juan - Playbill (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - The Hoffman Project - Notes by Mark Lamos, Director of The Hoffman Project (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - The Hoffman Project - Statement by Mark Lamos (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - The Hoffman Project - Production Meeting Notes (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - The Hoffman Project - A Description, if You Need a Description (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - The Hoffman Project - Written Research (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - The Hoffman Project - Visual Research (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - The Hoffman Project - Personal Observations (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - The Hoffman Project - Letter to Mark Lamos (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - The Hoffman Project - Stories by E.T.A. Hoffman (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - The Hoffman Project - Script by Ken Cavander (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - The Hoffman Project - Running Order of The Hoffman Project Performance (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - The Hoffman Project - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - The Master and Margarita - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Andrei Serban (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - The Master and Margarita - Production Cast List (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - The Master and Margarita - Scene Breakdown by Actor (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - The Master and Margarita - Property List (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - The Master and Margarita - Costume Production Reference: Costume Inventory Lists for All Characters (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - The Master and Margarita - Playbill (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - The Master and Margarita - Reviews (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Box 117
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Production Schedule (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Production Faxes (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Costume Production Reference: Principal Singers, Actress, Dancer, and Chorus: Visual Research, Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Costume Production Reference: Principal Singers, Actress, Dancer, and Chorus: Visual Research, Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Costume Production Reference: Dye Samples for Chorus Costumes (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Costume Production Reference: Dressing Lists for Principal Singers with photographs (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Production Photographs: Chorus Fitting (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Production Photographs (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Pre-production Publicity (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Playbill (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Salzburger Festspiele 1994 - Review (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Box 118
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Notes from Collaborative Meeting with Peter Sellars (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Production Faxes (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Costume Production Reference: Principal Singers, Actress & Dancer: Visual Research, Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Costume Production Reference: Chorus: Visual Research and Designs (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Production Photographs (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Pre-production Publicity (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - DeNederlandse Opera 1998 - Reviews (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Letters to Peter Sellars from Dunya Ramicova (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Production Contact List & Chorus Assignments (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Floor Plan (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Production Schedules (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Costume Production Schedule (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Production Correspondence (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Costume Production Reference (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Pre-production Publicity (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Los Angeles Philharmonic 2009 - Playbill (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Sydney Festival Winter 2010 - Production Contact Sheet (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Sydney Festival Winter 2010 - Production E-mails (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Sydney Festival Winter 2010 - Costume Production Reference (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Sydney Festival Winter 2010 - Playbill (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Oedipus Rex and Symphony of Psalms - Sydney Festival Winter 2010 - Review (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Box 119
    Oversized materials for Oedipus and the Symphony of Psalms
  - Box 120
    - Hercules - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars, Director of Hercules (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Hercules - Letter to Peter Sellars (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Hercules - Photographs of George Tsypin's Set Model for Hercules (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Hercules - Production Cast List (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Hercules - "Who/What/Where" Chart (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Hercules - Production E-mails (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Hercules - Letters from Dunya Ramicova to Hercules Principal Singers (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Hercules - Color and Fabric Plot for Male Chorus Costumes (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Hercules - Costume Production Reference (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Hercules - Wardrobe Running Sheets (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Hercules - Pre-production Publicity (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Hercules - Playbill (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Hercules - Playbill for Special Performance of Hercules for "War Follows Everyone Home" Event (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Hercules - Reviews (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Letter to Peter Sellars (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Production E-mail (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Costume Production Reference (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Packing List and Notes (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Costume Budget and Schedule (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Ojai Music Festival 2011 Master Production Schedule (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Ojai Music Festival 2011 Pre-Production Press Release (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Pre-Production Publicity (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Playbill (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - The Winds of Destiny - Reviews (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Box 121
    - Nixon in China - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (for original production in 1987) (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Nixon in China - Pictorial Research (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Nixon in China - Guide to Design Rendering Numbering System (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Nixon in China - Breakdown of Costumes According to their Style (either Western or Chinese) (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Nixon in China - List of Quick Change Times when Orchestra Cannot Stop (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Nixon in China - Costume Production Reference: Houston Grand Opera, Brooklyn Academy of Music, The John F. Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, The Netherlands Opera, Frankfurt Opera, and Maison de la Culture Bobigny (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Nixon in China - Costume Production Reference: Houston Grand Opera, Brooklyn Academy of Music, The John F. Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, The Netherlands Opera, Frankfurt Opera, and Maison de la Culture Bobigny (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Nixon in China - Costume Production Reference: Houston Grand Opera, Brooklyn Academy of Music, The John F. Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, The Netherlands Opera, Frankfurt Opera, and Maison de la Culture Bobigny (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Nixon in China - Costume Production Reference: Houston Grand Opera, Brooklyn Academy of Music, The John F. Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, The Netherlands Opera, Frankfurt Opera, and Maison de la Culture Bobigny (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Nixon in China - Character and Scene Breakdown for Male and Female Chorus and Extras, Los Angeles Music Center Opera (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Box 122
    - Nixon in China - Character and Scene Breakdown for Male and Female Chorus and Extras, Los Angeles Music Center Opera (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Nixon in China - Letter from DR to Karen Crychton, English National Opera Costume Director (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Nixon in China - Swatches for Some of English National Opera Costumes (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Nixon in China - Production E-mails (Metropolitan Opera Revival, 2010-2011) (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Nixon in China - Scene Breakdown (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Nixon in China - Costume Production Reference: Metropolitan Opera (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Nixon in China - Photographs of Makeup and Hair (Wigs) from Houston Grand Opera Production and Metropolitan Opera Production (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Nixon in China - Pre-production Publicity (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Nixon in China - Playbills (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Nixon in China - Reviews for Performances at Houston Grand Opera at the Wortham Music Center (Nixon in China opened the new Center on October 22, 1987) (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Box 123
    - Inspector General - Letter from Director Peter Sellars (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Inspector General - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Inspector General - Scene Design (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Inspector General - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Inspector General - Written Research and Design for Characters (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Inspector General - Costume Production Reference (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Inspector General - Playbill (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Production Contact Sheet (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Pictorial Research (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for all characters (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Costume Production Reference: Dressing Lists with Fabric Swatches (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Costume Production Reference: Costume Inventory Lists for Customs (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Costume Production Reference: Photographs of Actors Wearing Their Costumes (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Pre-production Publicity (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Playbills (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky - Reviews (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Box 124
    - The Peony Pavilion - Libretto (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Written Research and Ideas for Costumes in Peony Pavilion (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Pictorial Research (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Production Contact Information Lists (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Production Budget (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Production Faxes (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Preliminary Drawings (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Scene Design by George Tsypin (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Notes from Meetings with Hua Wenyi (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Pre-production Publicity (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Playbills (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - The Peony Pavilion - Reviews (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Box 125
    - The Merchant of Venice - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Production Contact Sheet (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Visual Research (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Costume Production Reference: Description of Costumes (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for all characters (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Pre-production Publicity (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Playbill (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - The Merchant of Venice - Reviews (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Box 126
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars and from Production Meetings (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Production Correspondence (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Costume Plot (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Costume Production Reference: Visual Research and Costume Lists for all characters (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Costume Production Reference: Visual Research and Costume Lists for all characters (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Costume Production Reference: Visual Research and Costume Lists for all characters (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Seven Deadly Sins - Production Photographs (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Box 127
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Co-Production Agreement (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Production Cast Lists (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Contact Information (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - General Description of Costumes (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Letter to Jennifer Green, Costume Director of San Francisco Opera (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Research for Fabric Drapes (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Color Plot (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Color Plot (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Note Regarding Photographing Singers in Costume Fittings (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Example Questionnaire Submitted to Dancers and Choristers (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - List of Dancers and Alternate Dancers with Note Regarding Wearing of Skirts or Trousers by Female Dancers (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Description of Costumes Worn by Ballet Dancers (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Costume Production Reference (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Costume Production Reference (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Box 128
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Costume Production Reference (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Costume Production Reference (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Pre-opening Publicity (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Playbills (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Reviews (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - The Death of Klinghoffer - Production Photographs (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Box 129
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Libretto (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Written Exploration of Design Ideas (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Written Research and Ideas for Specific Characters in Saint Francis of Assisi (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Integral Research Source (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Production Cast List (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Pictorial Research for Principal Singers (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Pictorial Research for Chorus (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Production Faxes (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Notes on Saint Francois d'Assise Costume Production (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Costume Production Reference (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Box 130
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Costume Production Reference (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Costume Production Reference (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Costume Production Reference (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Production Photographs (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Production Photographs (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Pre-opening Publicity (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Playbill (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Saint Francois d'Assise - Reviews (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Box 131
    - The Rake's Progress - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - The Rake's Progress - Written Research (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - The Rake's Progress - Production Cast List and Contact Sheet (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - The Rake's Progress - Production Faxes (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - The Rake's Progress - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - The Rake's Progress - Costume Production Reference: Principles and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Character Descriptions, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - The Rake's Progress - Costume Production Reference: Costume Inventory List created by Theatre du Chatelet Costume Shop staff for transfer of costumes to DeNederlandse Opera (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - The Rake's Progress - Costume Production Reference: Photographs (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - The Rake's Progress - Rehearsal Reports (Theatre du Chatelet) (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - The Rake's Progress - Playbill (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - The Rake's Progress - Reviews (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - The Rake's Progress - Production Cast List for Nederlandse Opera Performances (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - The Rake's Progress - Rehearsal Report (DeNederlandse Opera) (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - The Persians - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - The Persians - Production Contact List (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - The Persians - Written Exploration of Color Ideas (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - The Persians - Visual Research (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - The Persians - Costume Production Reference (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - The Persians - Visual Research for a Production Prop (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - The Persians - Production Budget (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - The Persians - Production Faxes (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - The Persians - Dressing Lists (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - The Persians - Playbill (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - The Persians - Review (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Box 132
    - Cosi Fan Tutte - Costume Plot and Scene Breakdown (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Cosi Fan Tutte - Production Cast List (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Cosi Fan Tutte - Costume Production Reference (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Cosi Fan Tutte - Playbill (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - Letter of Agreement from Arnall Downs, Assistant Costume Designer (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - Costume Production Budgets (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - Production (Rehearsal) Notes (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - Memo from Christopher Hunt (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - ORF Playbill (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - Reviews (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Mozart / Da Ponte Cycle - The United States of America Prague Quadrennial 1991 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Box 133
    - Don Giovanni (1987) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Don Giovanni (1987) - Costume Plot and Scene Breakdown (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Don Giovanni (1987) - Production Cast List (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Don Giovanni (1987) - Visual Research (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Don Giovanni (1987) - Costume Production Reference (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Don Giovanni (1987) - Playbill (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Don Giovanni (1989) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Don Giovanni (1989) - Peter Sellar Pre-show Presentation July 7, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Don Giovanni (1989) - Principles, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Costume Lists, Photographs from Final Fittings, and Fabric Swatches (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Don Giovanni (1989) - Principles, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Costume Lists, Photographs from Final Fittings, and Fabric Swatches (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Don Giovanni (1989) - Playbill (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Don Giovanni (1989) - Reviews (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Box 134
    - The Magic Flute - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - The Magic Flute - Production Cast List and Chorus Assignments (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - The Magic Flute - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - The Magic Flute - Color Copies of Adrianne Lobel's Set Design (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - The Magic Flute - Written Research (Box 134, Folder 5)